<?xml version="1.0"?>
<metadata xml:lang="en"><Esri><CreaDate>20220812</CreaDate><CreaTime>14535800</CreaTime><ArcGISFormat>1.0</ArcGISFormat><SyncOnce>TRUE</SyncOnce><ModDate>20231018</ModDate><ModTime>154828</ModTime><scaleRange><minScale>150000000</minScale><maxScale>5000</maxScale></scaleRange><ArcGISProfile>ItemDescription</ArcGISProfile></Esri><toolbox name="CI_Land_Index" alias="LandIndex"><arcToolboxHelpPath>c:\program files\arcgis\pro\Resources\Help\gp</arcToolboxHelpPath><toolsets/></toolbox><dataIdInfo><idCitation><resTitle>CI_Land_Index</resTitle></idCitation><idPurp>Step 1a is used for activity data that falls within major watersheds of stream order 7 or higher. These represent the most significant river systems and data from the headwaters of each drainage basin is included. A Land index (LI) value will be saved to point features representing the main estuaries of each major watershed. These points are then used in the coastal kernel density tool to determine impact.

Step 1b is used to process coastal land-based activity data that falls within coastal watersheds of stream order less than 7. The Cumulative Impact Mapping analysis will model the impact of these land-based activities within a specified impact distance from the coastline. </idPurp><idAbs>&lt;DIV STYLE="text-align:Left;"&gt;&lt;DIV&gt;&lt;DIV&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;The Land Index toolbox processes land-based activity data, depending on whether the activities occur within the boundaries of major watersheds, or whether the activities occur in coastal areas within impact distance of the ocean. The outputs of both tools will be pulled into the Coastal Kernel Density analysis at Step 3. &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</idAbs><idCredit>Created by Craig Schweitzer and Selina Agbayani (DFO, Sep 2023)</idCredit><searchKeys><keyword>Cumulative Impact Mapping</keyword><keyword>Data Preparation</keyword></searchKeys></dataIdInfo><distInfo><distributor><distorFormat><formatName>ArcToolbox Toolbox</formatName></distorFormat></distributor></distInfo><mdHrLv><ScopeCd value="005"/></mdHrLv><mdDateSt Sync="TRUE">20231018</mdDateSt></metadata>
