<?xml version="1.0"?>
<metadata xml:lang="en"><Esri><CreaDate>20230830</CreaDate><CreaTime>14353900</CreaTime><ArcGISFormat>1.0</ArcGISFormat><SyncOnce>TRUE</SyncOnce><ModDate>20231013</ModDate><ModTime>121254</ModTime><scaleRange><minScale>150000000</minScale><maxScale>5000</maxScale></scaleRange><ArcGISProfile>ItemDescription</ArcGISProfile></Esri><toolbox name="CI_MarineFootprint_Pro" alias="MarineFootprint"><arcToolboxHelpPath>c:\program files\arcgis\pro\Resources\Help\gp</arcToolboxHelpPath><toolsets/></toolbox><dataIdInfo><idCitation><resTitle>CI_MarineFootprint_Pro</resTitle></idCitation><idPurp></idPurp><idAbs>&lt;DIV STYLE="text-align:Left;"&gt;&lt;DIV&gt;&lt;DIV&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;The Marine Footprint analysis calculates the cumulative impact from activities that have an impact over a specific area and are represented by polygon spatial data. &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Data for all activities and habitats must go through Marine Footprint Steps 3-5 to be included in the cumulative impact score. Outputs from the Land Index and Coastal Kernel Density Toolboxes are used as inputs in Step 3 of the Marine Footprint Toolbox. &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN STYLE="font-weight:bold;text-decoration:underline;"&gt;Calculating Impact Scores: &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Step 1 calculates the relative intensity (RI), and Step 2 calculates the stressor weighted RI (Wtd_RI) which will be used in Step 3 to calculated area weighted impact scores. Outputs from the Land Index and Coastal Kernel Density Toolboxes are converted into polygons representing the footprint of the impact of coastal and land activities on the marine. Therefore, these outputs are inserted into the Marine Footprint toolbox at Step 3. &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN STYLE="font-weight:bold;text-decoration:underline;"&gt;Calculating Cumulative Impact Scores:&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Step 4 calculates sum impact scores per activity across all habitats. Step 5 is run in two parts. Part 1 calculates sum impact scores across activities per habitat, and Part 2 calculates cumulative impact scores across all activities and all habitats. &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;To calculate cumulative impact scores for sectors (i.e., a subset of activities such as fishing or coastal), Step 5 can be run for a subset of activities which are identified with a unique sector descriptor to identify sector specific output geodatabases and prefixes to identify sector specific output tables.  &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</idAbs><searchKeys><keyword>Cumulative Impact Mapping</keyword><keyword>activities</keyword><keyword>habitats</keyword><keyword>cumulative impact scores</keyword></searchKeys></dataIdInfo><distInfo><distributor><distorFormat><formatName>ArcToolbox Toolbox</formatName></distorFormat></distributor></distInfo><mdHrLv><ScopeCd value="005"/></mdHrLv><mdDateSt Sync="TRUE">20231006</mdDateSt></metadata>
